[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "What -- what's been going on there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": ".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Katrina"]}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "What do you say to the skeptics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, charity should begin at home and there's a tremendous amount of work being done and certainly we have to pay attention to -- you know, we haven't really dealt with Katrina.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "How much emotional energy are you expending on this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I spend, you know, hours a day on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Why does this cause mean so much to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I have to say, you have a very nice tie and I know you -- you could be George.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "How -- how close have you come to getting hurt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "You know, not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Have you discovered that you're braver than you may have thought you were?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "As a father, do you worry about George when he goes off on these crusades there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "The answer to that question is yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sudan", "Burma"]}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NNS", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "JJ", ":", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Why -- why are you constantly fighting this kind of uphill struggle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "I think -- I think a lot of times and I think most newsmen would agree, my father being one of them, that it's not just necessarily hard news sell the Sudan, it's a hard news sell virtual -- many, many of the hot spots around the world that it's, you know, it's hard to get Burma on the news.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Nick, as George's father again, do you get incensed on his behalf?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "You bet.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "And do you -- do you use maybe juicier language than that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Almost never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "George, do you -- do you believe there's going to be peace in Sudan in the next few years or are you quite pessimistic about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sudan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Are you worried for your own personal safety that the more high-profile you get?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "First of all, what was your feeling when those photographers decided to exact their horrific revenge and lay down their cameras?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "JJ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Well, I love the fact that -- that they covered themselves not taking pictures.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sudan"]}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "It's not just the Sudan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Do they have any rights to privacy when they do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "You know, I have no -- I couldn't really argue for or against that issue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Is there some way that a person may be allowed to go out and have dinner with his family or her family without having a camera in the nose of the three year old?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Having whacked the media, I guess, for that part of it, obviously -- maybe come back to you, George, here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "So there is the -- I mean, there is a deal with the devil to be struck, isn't there, when it's important?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Well, the -- the -- but the deal is struck long before, you know, I got involved.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "What -- where do you think the line should be drawn here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "You know, look, I thought that President Obama gave, as he does when -- when he needs to -- he gave one of the greatest speeches I've heard in a long, long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "It can't be any worse than being a movie star, can it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Really, I mean, honestly, my job is as good as they get.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "I -- do you think he's better looking than I am?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Because we see that working so well right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "You've got to hope, George.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Is this a half-an-hour show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "We're making it a three-parter, now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "What values do you think they instilled in you as a young -- a young George?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "My father taught me never to mix grain and grape at a very young age.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "But to be serious -- to be serious, what -- what did they teach you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ":", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Now, listen, you know, I'm very lucky.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "POS", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "What -- what's been the proudest you've ever been of George and also the least proud?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Well let's see, the proudest I have been of George is -- you know, there's something about -- let me put it this way.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "ORGAN: What's the naughtiest he's ever been would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "You know, naughty, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "What was -- what was important to you that when he grew up, he -- he'd adhere to a certain code of behavior as far as you're concerned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "You know, Piers, I know what -- I know what you mean here and I'd like to think that I had something to do with both of the kids and how they turned out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "But if you were to actually take your life to date, if you could replay one moment in your life before you die, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Well, you know, I was thinking about that when you asked the question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "But it turns out it's actually this -- I mean you -- you do get malaria flare ups quite regularly, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Oh, you wouldn't swap his life for yours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "That's a great title, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "It's perfect one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "George, is he right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Do you think you'll ever -- will you ever re-marry, George?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Here we go.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "I'm allowed one, am I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "-- for the last segment to pull it out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Piers, are you married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I just got re-married.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Oh, you did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "ORGAN: Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "You could give it all to these people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "Well, I don't think -- I don't ever wish I wasn't super rich.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Would you tell them that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "I will.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Do you think he's going to run?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "I think he might.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]